Guide to the Hasia Diner Papers, 1970-2012 MC.153
New York University Archives
- Series I: Research Notes, 20561
  - Subseries F: Lower East Side Memories, 238686
    - References Not Used, undated; 238719 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Manuscript Edits, 1999; 238720 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - The Time That Was Then- Notes and Copies, undated; 238721 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Kosher Laws, undated; 238722 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Presentation of Jewish Foodways, undated; 238736 (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Jewish Infrastructure and Novelty, undated; 238737 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Jewish Oral Histories from Rochester, 1999; 238738 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Jewish Culture, undated; 238739 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Rough Draft, undated; 238740 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Notes, undated; 238741 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Conclusion for Chapter 1, undated; 238744 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - The American Hebrew- articles and notes (1 of 2), undated; 238747 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - The American Hebrew- articles and notes (2 of 2), undated; 238748 (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Chapter on Contemporary LES Texts, undated; 238749 (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Xeroxed Materials and Drafts for Chapter 1, undated; 238750 (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Jewish Housing, undated; 238752 (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - Additions for Chap. Hist. Text, undated; 238758 (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - History Chapter 2 (1 of 2), undated; 238759 (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - History Chapter 2 (2 of 2), undated; 238760 (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - Permission for MCNY Photos, undated; 238763 (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - Contact Information, undated; 238766 (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - Big Onion Information, undated; 238768 (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - Tenement Museum, undated; 238774 (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - Eldridge Street Project, undates; 238776 (Box 16, Folder 31)
    - The Jazz Singer- notes and copies, undated; 238907 (Box 16, Folder 32)
    - Permission for Photos, 1998; 238909 (Box 16, Folder 34)
    - Hester Street Film, 1998; 238918 (Box 16, Folder 34)
    - Images for LES, undated; 238919 (Box 16, Folder 35)
    - FOX permission for Simpsons, undated; 238920 (Box 16, Folder 36)
    - UAHC Notes, undated; 238924 (Box 16, Folder 37)
    - Information on Maude Weisser's Minatures, undated; 238925 (Box 16, Folder 38)
    - Maude Weisser's Minature's- color photos, undated; 238926 (Box 16, Folder 39)
    - Maude Weisser's Minatures- black and white photos, undated; 238928 (Box 16, Folder 40)
    - Maude Weisser's Minatures- negatives, undated; 238935 (Box 16, Folder 41)
    - Leo's Delancey Street Deli Photos, undated; 238936 (Box 16, Folder 42)
    - Floppy Disks, undated; 238937 (Box 16, Folder 43)
  - Subseries G: We Remember with Reverance and Love, 238970
    - Hebrew Publishing, 2008; 238971 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - The New York Review, 2009; 238972 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - New Directions in Jewish Theology in America booklet, 1994; 238973 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - The Americanization of the Holocaust booklet, 1995; 238974 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Materials from YIVO, undated; 238975 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Art Resource Information, undated; 238976 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Permissions for Jewish Theological Seminary of America, 2008; 238977 (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Yeshiva Flatbush Permissions, 2008; 238978 (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Newberry Library Permissions, 2008; 238979 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - SAJ Permissions, undated; 238980 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - American Jewish Historical Society Permissions, 2008; 238981 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Shengold Permissions, 2008; 238982 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - American Jewish Archives Permissions, 2008; 238983 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Jewish Book Annual, undated; 238984 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - American Jewish Historical Society SCA, undated; 238985 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - List of Sources, undated; 238986 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Meyer Barkai Permissions, undated; 238987 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - URJ Press Permissions, 2008; 238988 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - United Synagogue Commission Permission, 2008; 238989 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Bloch Publishing Permissions, 2008; 238990 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Temple University Archives Photocopies, 2008; 238991 (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - Spertus Permissions, 2008; 238992 (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - YIVO User Agreements, undated; 238993 (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - Jewish Newspaper Clipping, 2008; 238994 (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - Yeshiva University Archive Material, undated; 238995 (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - Renee and Chaim Gross Foundation, 2008; 238996 (Box 17, Folder 26)
    - Tamiment Archives Premissions, 2008; 238997 (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - Carnegie Mellon Libraries, undated; 238998 (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - Cover of the Book, undated; 238999 (Box 17, Folder 29)
    - NYU Press Copy Edit Info, 2008; 239000 (Box 17, Folder 30)
    - The Sentinel photocopies, undated; 239001 (Box 17, Folder 31)
    - Images for Book, undated; 239002 (Box 17, Folder 32)
    - Beth Halpen's Master Thesis, undated; 239003 (Box 17, Folder 33)
    - Mia Sara Bruch's Presentation on American Jews, 2005; 239006 (Box 17, Folder 34)
    - Naomi Sage Paper, 2004; 239008 (Box 17, Folder 35)
    - Kenneth Waltzer Paper, 2005; 239017 (Box 17, Folder 36)
    - Laura Jockusch Dissertation Proposal, 2003; 239018 (Box 17, Folder 37)
    - Dana Herman Paper, undated; 239019 (Box 17, Folder 38)
    - Carpenter Paper, undated; 239020 (Box 17, Folder 39)
    - Gershon Greenberg Paper, 2005; 239021 (Box 17, Folder 40)
    - Natalia Aleksium Paper, undated; 239022 (Box 17, Folder 41)
    - David Biale Paper, undated; 239023 (Box 17, Folder 42)
    - Holocaust Education Week in Toronto Essay, 2004; 239055 (Box 17, Folder 43)
    - David Weinstein Paper, undated; 239056 (Box 17, Folder 44)
    - Michael Marrus Paper, 2005; 239066 (Box 17, Folder 45)
    - Yigal Sklarin Paper, undated; 239067 (Box 17, Folder 46)
    - Purple Notebook, undated; 239070 (Box 17, Folder 47)
    - Red Notebook, undated; 239071 (Box 17, Folder 48)
    - Handwritten Notes, undated; 239072 (Box 17, Folder 49)
    - Bobcat Records, undated; 239073 (Box 17, Folder 50)
    - The 2001 SWIG Lecture Pamphlet, 239074 (Box 17, Folder 51)
    - American Jewish Yearbook (1 of 2), undated; 239075 (Box 17, Folder 52)
    - American Jewish Yearbook (2 of 2), undated; 239076 (Box 17, Folder 53)
    - Miscellaneous Notes, undated; 239077 (Box 17, Folder 54)
    - Center for Jewish History Photocopy Request, 2003; 239078 (Box 17, Folder 55)
    - Tamiment Library Photocopy Requests, 2004; 239203 (Box 17, Folder 56)
    - The Chronicle Review, 2009; 239204 (Box 17, Folder 57)
    - Center for Jewish History Request Forms, 2004; 239205 (Box 17, Folder 58)
    - Sources used, undated; 239206 (Box 17, Folder 59)
    - NYPL Records, 2004; 239207 (Box 17, Folder 60)
    - Book Reviews, undated; 239208 (Box 17, Folder 61)
    - Sources that were too early or too late, undated; 239209 (Box 17, Folder 62)
    - "Junk", undated; 239210 (Box 17, Folder 63)
    - Israel Goldberg, undated; 239211 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Fanny Goldstein Papers (1 of 2), undated; 239212 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Fanny Goldstein Papers (2 of 2), undated; 239213 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Eliezer Greenberg, undated; 239214 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Meyer Greenberg Papers, undated; 239215 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Halevy Choral Society, undated; 239216 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Jewish Book Annual (1 of 2), undated; 239217 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Jewish Book Annual (2 of 2), undated; 239218 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Jewish Community Council Greater Washington, undated; 239221 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Jewish Education Magazine (1 of 2), undated; 239222 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Jewish Education Magazine (2 of 2), undated; 239223 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Jewish Family and Children Services, undated; 239224 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Hebrew Union College Annual, undated; 239225 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Intercollegiate Zionist and Federation of America, undated; 239227 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Louis Harap Material, undated; 239232 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Camp Hemshekh, undated; 239233 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Rhea Hirsch, undated; 239234 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Holocaust Relates Articles in Yiddish Journals, undated; 239235 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Jewish Forum Material, undated; 239236 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Jewish Frontier notes and copies, undated; 239237 (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Jewish Frontier (Original copy), 1958; 239238 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Jewish Labor Committee (1 of 2), undated; 239239 (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - Jewish Labor Committee (2 of 2), undated; 239240 (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Jewish Museum- notes, undated; 239247 (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Jewish Reconstruction Foundation Papers, undated; 239248 (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - Jewish Social Studies Quarterly (1 of 2), undated; 239249 (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - Jewish Social Studies Quarterly (2 of 2), undated; 239250 (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - Jewish Spectator (1 of 2), undated; 239257 (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - Jewish Spectator (2 of 2), undated; 239258 (Box 18, Folder 27)
    - Jewish Student Organizations Collection, undated; 239259 (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - Jewish Telegraphic Agency News, undated; 239260 (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - Jewish Theological Seminary Misc., undated; 239262 (Box 18, Folder 29)
    - Jewish War Veterans, undated; 239265 (Box 18, Folder 30)
    - American Joint Distribution Committee, undated; 239266 (Box 18, Folder 31)
    - Judaism (Quarterly), undated; 239267 (Box 18, Folder 32)
    - Label Katz Papers (1of 2), undated; 239268 (Box 18, Folder 33)
    - Label Katz Papers (2 of 2), undated; 239269 (Box 18, Folder 34)
    - Labor Zionist Organization of American (Chicago) (1 of 2), undated; 239270 (Box 18, Folder 35)
    - Labor Zionist Organization of America (Chicago) (2 of 2), undated; 239271 (Box 18, Folder 36)
    - Louis Lamed Papers, undated; 239275 (Box 18, Folder 37)
    - Kolbuszowa Relief Association, undated; 239276 (Box 18, Folder 38)
    - Lema'an Hayeled, undated; 239277 (Box 18, Folder 39)
    - Raphael Lempkin papers, undated; 239278 (Box 18, Folder 40)
    - Leo Baeck Institute, undated; 239280 (Box 18, Folder 41)
    - Menorah Journal Notes, undated; 239284 (Box 18, Folder 42)
    - Midstream Magazine (1 of 2), undated; 239285 (Box 18, Folder 43)
    - Midstream Magazine (2 of 2), undated; 239286 (Box 18, Folder 44)
    - Midwest Jewish Council, undated; 239287 (Box 18, Folder 45)
    - Joseph Baron Papers, undated; 239288 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Salo Baron Papers, undated; 239289 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Bernstein (1 of 4), undated; 239296 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Bernstein (2 of 4), undated; 239297 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Bernstein (3 of 4), undated; 239298 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Bernstein (4 of 4), undated; 239299 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - American Memorial to the 6 million, undated; 239300 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Anti-Organization League, undated; 239301 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Artists, undated; 239302 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - American Jewish Yearbook (1954-1967) (1 of 2), undated; 239303 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - American Jewish Yearbook (1954-1967) (2 of 2), 239304 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - American Jewish Historical Society, undated; 239305 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - American Jewish Yearbook (1945-1953) (1 of 2), undated; 239306 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - American Jewish Yearbook (1945-1953) (2 of 2), undated; 239322 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - American Jewish Congress (1 of 4), undated; 239323 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - American Jewish Congress (2 of 4), undated; 239324 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - American Jewish Congress (3 of 4), undated; 239325 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - American Jewish Congress (4 of 4), undated; 239326 (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Paul Abelson Papers, undated; 239327 (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Academy Memoirs, undated; 239328 (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - Bessie Adel Papers, undated; 239329 (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - American Federation for Polish Jews, undated; 239330 (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - American Jewish Committees, undated; 239331 (Box 19, Folder 23)
    - American Jewish Archives, undated; 239332 (Box 19, Folder 24)
    - World Over Magazine, undated; 239333 (Box 19, Folder 25)
    - Yiddish Journal, 1973; 239334 (Box 19, Folder 26)
    - Studies in Contemporary Jewry, 2004; 239335 (Box 19, Folder 27)
    - Songbook of the Cejwin Camps, 1959; 239336 (Box 19, Folder 28)
    - Songbook of the Cejwin Camps, 1963; 239337 (Box 19, Folder 29)
    - Yiddish Journal, 1973-1974; 239338 (Box 19, Folder 30)
    - P'tsah B'Zemer Songbook, undated; 239339 (Box 19, Folder 31)
    - Journal of Modern Jewish Studies, 2004; 239340 (Box 19, Folder 32)
    - "Polish Historiography of the Holocaust" article, 2004; 239341 (Box 19, Folder 33)
    - Notebook, undated; 239342 (Box 19, Folder 34)
    - Seder Service Booklet, undated; 239343 (Box 19, Folder 35)
    - Notes, undated; 239344 (Box 19, Folder 36)
    - East European Jewish Affairs Journal, 2003; 239345 (Box 19, Folder 37)
    - AJHS Notes, undated; 239346 (Box 19, Folder 38)
    - Holocaust Commemoration in Vancouver, BC, 2001; 239347 (Box 19, Folder 39)
    - "In the Bond of Life Article', undated; 239348 (Box 19, Folder 40)
    - Seder Ritual Committee, undated; 239349 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Shalom Aleichem Folk Foundation, undated; 239350 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Leo Schwartz Papers, undated; 239351 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Slomowitz papers, undated; 239352 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Synagogue Council of America (1 of 4), undated; 239353 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Synagogue Council of America (2 of 4), undated; 239354 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Synagogue Council of America (3 of 4), undated; 239355 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Synagogue Council of America (4 of 4), undated; 239356 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Sophie Tucker Papers, undated; 239357 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Union Institute, undated; 239358 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Vaad Hatzalah, undated; 239359 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - The Week in Religion, undated; 239360 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Women of Reform Judaism Papers, undated; 239361 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Howard Weinshell Papers, undated; 239362 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Wisconsin Society for Jewish Learning, undated; 239363 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Yad Vashem (1 of 6), undated; 239364 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Yad Vashem (2 of 6), undated; 239365 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Yad Vashem (3 of 6), undated; 239366 (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - Yad Vashem (4 of 6), undated; 239367 (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - Yad Vashem (5 of 6), undated; 239368 (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - Yad Vashem (6 of 6), undated; 239369 (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - YIVO (Yedios) (1 of 3), undated; 239370 (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - YIVO (Yedios) (2 of 3), undated; 239371 (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - YIVO (Yedios) (3 of 3), undated; 239372 (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - Young Judea (The Senior) (1 of 2), undated; 239373 (Box 20, Folder 24)
    - Young Judea (The Senior) (2 of 2), undated; 239374 (Box 20, Folder 25)
    - Young Israel, undated; 239615 (Box 20, Folder 26)
    - Maurice Zigmond, undated; 239616 (Box 20, Folder 27)
    - Youth and Nation, undated; 239617 (Box 20, Folder 28)
    - Zionist Organization of America pamphlets, undated; 239618 (Box 20, Folder 29)
    - A 1945-1962 Books, undated; 239619 (Box 20, Folder 30)
    - B, C 1945-1962 Books, undated; 239620 (Box 20, Folder 31)
    - D, E, F, G 1945-1962 Books (1 of 2), undated; 239621 (Box 20, Folder 32)
    - D, E, F, G 1945-1962 Books (2 of 2), undated; 239622 (Box 20, Folder 33)
    - H, I, J 1945-1962 Books (1 of 2), undated; 239623 (Box 20, Folder 34)
    - H, I, J 1945-1962 Books (2 of 2), undated; 239624 (Box 20, Folder 35)
    - K, L, M 1945-1962 Books (1 of 3), undated; 239628 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - K, L, M 1945-1962 Books (2 of 3), undated; 239629 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - K, L, M 1945-1962 Books (3 of 3), undated; 239630 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - N, O, P 1945-1962 Books, undated; 239631 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Q, R, S 1945-1962 Books (1 of 3), undated; 239632 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Q, R, S 1945-1962 Books (2 of 3), undated; 239633 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Q, R, S 1945-1962 Books (3 of 3), undated; 239634 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - T, U, V 1945-1962 Books, undated; 239635 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - W, X, Y, Z 1945-1962 Books, undated; 239636 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - A-F Post 1962 Books (1 of 3), undated; 239637 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - A-F Post 1962 Books (2 of 3), undated; 239638 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - A-F Post 1962 Books (3 of 3), undated; 239639 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - G-M Post 1962 Books (1 of 2), undated; 239640 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - G-M Post 1962 Books (2 of 2), undated; 239641 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - N-S Post 1962 Books (1 of 3), undated; 239642 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - N-S Post 1962 Bokos (2 of 3), undated; 239643 (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - N-S Post 1962 (3 of 3), undated; 239644 (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - T-Z Post 1962, undated; 239645 (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Minkoff (1 of 3), undated; 239918 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Minkoff (2 of 3), undated; 239919 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Minkoff (3 of3), undated; 239920 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Misc. for Ch. 3, undated; 239921 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Misc. Magazine (1 of 3), undated; 239922 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Misc. Magazines (2 of 3), undated; 239923 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Misc. Magazines (3 of3), undated; 239943 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Misc. Music, undated; 239944 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Paul Moni, undated; 239945 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - National Council of Jewish Women, undated; 239951 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - National Federation of Temple Sisterhoods (1 of2), undated; 239952 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - National Federation of Temple Sisterhoods (2 of 2), undated; 239953 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - National Federation of Temple Youth, undated; 239954 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - National Jewish Music Council, undated; 239955 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Paul O'Dwyer, undated; 239956 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Olin Sang Ruby, undated; 239958 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - ORT, undated; 239959 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - Jacob Pat, undated; 239960 (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - The Pedagogic Reporter, undated; 239961 (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - Josh Perelman, undated; 239963 (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - Koppel Pinson Papers, undated; 239964 (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - Molly Picon, undated; 239965 (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - Poetry, undated; 239969 (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - Plays, Pageant, Cantata, undated; 239970 (Box 22, Folder 23)
    - Joachim Prinz (1 of 2), undated; 240708 (Box 22, Folder 24)
    - Joachim Prinz (2 of 2), undated; 240709 (Box 22, Folder 25)
    - Rabbinical Council of America (Holiday Sermons), undated; 240710 (Box 22, Folder 26)
    - Ramah, undated; 240711 (Box 22, Folder 27)
    - Cecilia Razovsky, undated; 240712 (Box 22, Folder 28)
    - Religious Zionists of America, undated; 240713 (Box 22, Folder 29)
    - Rescue Children, INC, undated; 240714 (Box 22, Folder 30)
    - Bernard Richards, undated; 240715 (Box 22, Folder 31)
    - Robison Family Papers, undated; 240725 (Box 22, Folder 32)
    - Rode F. Shalom, undated; 240726 (Box 22, Folder 33)
    - William F. Rosenblum, undated; 240727 (Box 22, Folder 34)
    - Isaac Rosenfeld, undated; 240728 (Box 22, Folder 35)
    - Herman Rubenovitz, undated; 240729 (Box 22, Folder 36)
    - Society for the Advancement of Judaism, undated; 240730 (Box 22, Folder 37)
    - Boris Molar (Between You and Me) (1 of 2), undated; 240731 (Box 22, Folder 38)
    - Boris Molar (Between You and Me) (2 of 2), undated; 240732 (Box 22, Folder 39)
    - Schallek News, undated; 240733 (Box 22, Folder 40)
    - Schappes (1 of 2), undated; 240734 (Box 22, Folder 41)
    - Schappes (2 of 2), undated; 240735 (Box 22, Folder 42)
    - Dore Scharry, undated; 240736 (Box 22, Folder 43)
    - Hyman Schulson, undated; 240737 (Box 22, Folder 44)
    - Shalom Secunda, undated; 240738 (Box 22, Folder 45)
    - NYPL Receipts, 2005; 240752 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - American Jewish Archives Publication Form, 2008; 240754 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Pittsburgh Jewish Newspaper Project, 2008; 240755 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Copies of Articles A-B, unknown; 240760 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Copies of Articles C-D, undated; 240761 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Copies of Articles E-F, undated; 240762 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Copies of Articles G, undated; 240765 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Copies of Articles H-K, unknown; 240766 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Copies of Articles L-M, unknown; 240767 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Copies of Articles N-P, undated; 240768 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Copies of Articles R, undated; 240769 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Copies of Articles S, undated; 240770 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Copies of Articles T-Y, undated; 240775 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Notebook, undated; 240776 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Articles 1945-1962, undated; 240777 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Articles Post 1962 (1of 2), undated; 240778 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Articles Post 1962 (2 of 2), undated; 240779 (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - Book Reviews, 240786 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Thesis Approval Sheet: Carl Samuel Choper, undated; 240787 (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - Chapter 5 of Diane Leon-Ferdico's Thesis, undated; 240788 (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - Picking up the Pieces Thesis, 1997; 240789 (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - Select Pages from Laura Jackson's Thesis, undated; 240790 (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - Jason Kalman Thesis Chapter 5, unknown; 240791 (Box 23, Folder 22)
    - Cover page of Cecile Esther Kuznitz's thesis, undated; 240792 (Box 23, Folder 23)
    - Holocaust Art in America Essay, undated; 240793 (Box 23, Folder 24)
    - "Delayed Pilgrims" Roberta Newman thesis (1 of 2), undated; 240794 (Box 23, Folder 25)
    - 'Delayed Pilgrims" by Roberta Newman thesis (2 of2), undated; 240795 (Box 23, Folder 25)
    - American Responses to Holocaust Essay, undated; 240800 (Box 23, Folder 26)
    - "Defining Lessons" by Rona Sheramy, undated; 240801 (Box 23, Folder 27)
    - Lists of Films, undated; 240837 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - "Forward", undated; 240838 (Box 24, File 2)
    - Lillian Friedberg Papers, undated; 240839 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Friedman, Philip (1of 2), undated; 240840 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Friedman, Philip (2 of 2), undated; 240844 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Fardar, S and G, undated; 240859 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Furrows (1 of 2), undated; 240860 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Furrows (2 of 2), undated; 240861 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Commentary Magazine Notes, undated; 240865 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Congregation Tifereth Joseph, Anshei Prezemysl (notes), undated; 240866 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Congress for Jewish Culture, undated; 240867 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Emails regarding the book, 2005-2006; 240868 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Conservative Judaism Journal, undated; 240869 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Debrest, Harold, undated; 240870 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Der Tog, undated; 240872 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Eternal Light (1 of 3), undated; 240873 (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - Eternal Light (2 of 3), undated; 240877 (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - Eternal Light (3 of 3), undated; 240878 (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - Calemson, Jesse, undated; 240879 (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - Cantor's Institute, undated; 240880 (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - Centre de Documentation Juive Contemp. In Paris, undated; 240896 (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - Central Orthodox Committee, undated; 240897 (Box 24, Folder 22)
    - Cincinnati JCRC (1 of 2), undated; 240898 (Box 24, Folder 23)
    - Cincinnati JCRC (2 of 2), undated; 240899 (Box 24, Folder 24)
    - Claims Conference, undated; 240912 (Box 24, Folder 25)
    - Cogan, Edna, undated; 240913 (Box 24, Folder 26)
    - Cohen, Jacob, undated; 240917 (Box 24, Folder 27)
    - Bibliographies, undated; 240937 (Box 24, Folder 28)
    - Bletter, undated; 240938 (Box 24, Folder 29)
    - Bloch Publishing, undated; 240939 (Box 24, Folder 30)